Good morning, sleepyheads.
It is day eight of testing the top 10 tourist attractions in America.
Yesterday, we did a road trip along the Pacific Coast Highway, ending at the Golden Gate Bridge in San Francisco.
Today, we are staying in California because we are going to...
Los Angeles!
We've got a packed day in LA.
It's going to be so fun.
But before we go to the airport...
Morning!
First things first, gotta brush my teeth.
Don't want anyone in LA looking at me funny.
I put on deodorant on one armpit.
I shaved my beard.
I have a really long beard right now, so I shave it off.
And lastly, some cologne to attract my wife.
And just like that, I'm ready for the day.
Let's go to the car.
Let's go to the airport.
Time to soak up our last moments in the convertible.
We drove back across the Golden Gate Bridge to the airport.
Thank you, Shopify, for sponsoring our bucket list.
We took off towards LA on a very, very short flight.
While there are many things to do in Los Angeles as a tourist, I have selected three things that I think are going to be really fun.
Number one, Santa Monica Pier.
It is one of the most visited landmarks in California.
It has 8 million visitors per year.
And it has a Ferris wheel.
I'm scared of Ferris wheels.
You're not going to make me go on that, right?
Number two, the Hollywood sign.
It's one of the most photographed signs in the entire world.
You can hike to it.
You can drive to it.
Either way is fun.
And number three, we are going to a Dodgers baseball game.
I felt like going to a baseball game in this series is a must.
It's America's favorite pastime, and the Dodgers are one of the most famous sports teams.
Also, they sell like 2 million hot dogs every year, so I foresee more glizzies in our future.
It's a quick flight to LA, so we'll see you on the ground.
New tourist attraction unlocked!
We took an hour-long Uber to our first tourist attraction.
We have arrived to Santa Monica Pier!
Hey, Santa Monica Pier!
It's going to be an eventful day here in LA.
And don't forget why we're doing this.
Gosh dang it, it's important.
On the scale of underrated to overrated, people generally consider Santa Monica Pier to be overrated, unfortunately.
Like I said before, it is one of the most visited tourist attractions, so let's try to see what's going on here with some of the reviews.
Alana said, "Not much to see or do.
It was boring and kind of dirty.
Junkie merch, don't buy it.
Don't eat funnel cake.
Don't bring any money.
One star."
I bought this hat from a hat stand and Haley bought that cardigan from Bubba Gump's.
It's actually really nice cardigan.
Yeah, I mean, look, it's got stars on it.
It's really good.
Semi-quincentennial vibes.
Exactly.
Ezra's review is crazy.
"Overcrowded.
The GTA 5 Santa Monica is 100% better.
I would rather just play the game than come back.
Ferris wheel is busted, bro.
One star."
Ezra's a big hater.
I've never seen someone that upset about a Ferris wheel.
Okay, well, the reviews have been proven wrong before.
So let's see what we think about Santa Monica Pier.
Let's have some fun.
Let's do it without the Ferris wheel, of course.
There's a show going on.
We got 25 seconds.
We don't know what they're about to do, but a large crowd of tourists began forming in anticipation of this show.
We're ready for it.
We got 10 seconds.
If you guys are ready for your show, everybody say yeah.
Yeah.
Oh, beautiful.
They started counting down from 30 seconds again, so we just decided to do other stuff.
All of the rides on this pier look kind of terrifying.
So we started with the easy stuff.
I won Haley a cat Mario plushie, which is pretty romantic.
Let's go, Haley.
Yeah!
And after a much-needed $5 photo booth experience, we got some breakfast from the Funnel Cake guy.
Santa Monica Pier is really just like a carnival.
It's just a carnival on the beach.
It is now time for us to go on the Ferris wheel.
Mario's joining us for this ride.
Third wheel.
Oh my gosh.
This is awesome.
Look at that view.
I'm Not going.
We're going to go.
Right?
I have Mario.
What?
He's got nothing on me.
If you were here, what ride would you go on?
I'm ready to get off the Ferris wheel.
Y'all, these guys just started dancing.
They were counting down from 30 seconds for an hour.
They're actually really good, though.
Haley and I stopped in at a taco place right by the Santa Monica Pier.
It's called Taco 1986.
For lunch, we have easily one of our favorite foods in the world: al pastor tacos.
Mario, what do you think about this?
Haley, cheers.
Cheers.
Mm.
Those might be the best corn tortillas I've ever had.
Those are so good.
I feel like I have so many memories in this area of Los Angeles.
In 2022, when I did the Penny series, I started at Venice Beach.
I spent like five days in LA, starting from a penny and working my way up to be able to get a ticket to Las Vegas.
Good times.
It's pretty diabolical.
The first calories of our day was funnel cake.
The one thing everyone says about Los Angeles is it takes a long time to drive places.
Our next stop is the Hollywood sign, and it's going to take like an hour to get there.
So we're going to eat this food as quick as we can so we can go to the Hollywood sign.
You totally caught us hanging out at Lake Hollywood Park at the Hollywood sign.
We can't quite see the Hollywood sign from here, but it's just behind us.
It's honestly such a vibe here at this park.
There's a fruit stand.
We purchased a large cup of fruit and ate it while basking in the sun.
Honestly, I really needed this.
This is the first time in this whole series I felt like I can just relax.
What about on the Guardians of the Galaxy ride?
Oh my gosh.
You're a troll.
Who is this guy anyway?
You got him for me.
Yeah, I didn't expect him to be attached to the hip.
A lot of tourists think that the Hollywood sign is actually underrated as a tourist attraction, which kind of surprises me because it is just a sign.
Yeah, because what are they talking about?
The hike?
The photo op?
Let's find out.
Suzanne wrote, "This is a must do in Los Angeles.
Got great pictures and the kids loved it.
Get their fruit.
Five stars."
That's exactly what we did, Suzanne.
And we haven't actually seen the sign yet, but looking forward to it.
Toby's review is awesome.
He said, "The Hollywood sign is a symbol of American dream.
We saw it from distance, but it's enough for me.
So inspired.
Five stars."
You want to see the picture Toby's talking about?
Yes, of course.
Auto-zone in the Hollywood sign.
I genuinely could not see the sign initially in this photo.
Oh, man.
I'm really enjoying just sitting in this grass, but we're going to hike up a little bit further, and we should have eyes on the Hollywood sign.
Let's have eyes on the Hollywood sign.
Yes.
I pulled a prank on Haley and made her think I was losing control down the hill.
I'm so funny.
Guys, I present to you the Hollywood sign.
Right there.
That one's going on the fridge.
That's a good picture.
I like it.
Well, we got some banger photos.
Also got one of Mario.
Had to snap a flick for my boy.
Really cool to see the Hollywood sign up this close.
And it's a beautiful day here in Los Angeles.
So you really have so much to be grateful for and so much to be happy about in this moment right now.
You couldn't have said it better myself.
As you can tell by the sun, it is now midday here in LA.
And Haley and I have a baseball game this evening.
We're going to the Dodgers game.
Very exciting.
We need somewhere to go hang out until then.
We're over here now at Dodger Stadium.
Ryan, you're not going to believe this, but a lot of people say a Dodgers game is underrated.
It's true.
Let me read you some of the reviews.
Zebra Sky says, "Oh look, they have a little scrapbooking profile photo.
Dodger Stadium is always a treat, not a bad seat in the house.
Get a Dodger dog, or two, or three, or four.
Five stars."
The Dodger dog is their hot dog.
We might just have to get two.
Or three or four.
Nah, uh, seriously, we probably shouldn't eat that many.
John TakesNoL says, "Oldest park west of the Mississippi.
Must be on your baseball bucket list.
Even if you're not a Dodger fan, get your butt over here.
Five stars."
That's crazy, John.
That's exactly what we did.
We literally did that.
I feel a little weird wearing all of this Dodgers merchandise because I grew up a Houston Astros fan, and I'm still a Houston Astros fan.
But today I am serving a greater purpose, alright?
I am a generic tourist.
And I feel conflicted because I just threw the first pitch for the Miami Marlins, which the Dodgers are going against today.
We got all kinds of moral dilemmas arising right now, but I am very excited.
I love a baseball game.
I think out of all the sports, it's probably the most fun to watch in person.
I hope there's a guy saying hot dogs.
Wasn't that good?
That was really good.
I didn't know you could do that.
I didn't either.
We arrived at the Dodger Stadium early.
We're here two hours before the game starts, and we thought we were some weirdos for showing up that early, but there are so many people here.
We even went shopping at Target before this, walked inside, and who do I see?
This guy is everywhere.
My goodness.
Good news though, I was able to find Joyride at Target.
As you know, Joyride is my candy.
My dream is to make it the number one candy in America.
And June 13th is Joyride Day.
It's right around the corner at this point.
We are going to set a new world record.
It's going to be done.
All you have to do to be a part of this world record is go to a store, take a photo with a bag of
Joyride, upload it to Instagram with your state and the location and hashtag JoyrideDay2026.
And that's it.
We need 200 people from every US state to set this world record.
And I think it can be done.
You can RSVP for Joyride Day through the link in the description.
Click the big green button and choose your store.
There's only a few more days to RSVP before Joyride Day.
We have over 30,000 of you guys so far who have already said you're going to participate in this world record.
These are the states that don't have 200 people RSVP'd yet.
If you live here or know anyone who does, please tell them about this.
Shout out to the Joyride Runners doing the exact same thing I just did.
You guys are the best.
I love seeing these photos every day.
I think the doors are opening to the stadium, so we're going to go get in line.
This is so fun.
Let's go Dodgers!
All right.
You guys ever tried the Dodgers dog?
I have.
You have?
You like it?
Yeah, it's good.
It's good.
All right.
I want to try the burger today, though.
Oh, the burger.
All right.
All right, guys.
Y'all have a good one.
Likewise.
My desire is to catch a home run today.
We just walked into the stadium, and the vibes are already electric.
We found this station where they let you make a baseball card out of yourself.
Yeah, of course we did it.
I want a baseball card of me and my wife.
And they put it in a protective sleeve so it'll be mint condition.
Uh...
Why she gotta bang it like that?
Still looks sick.
Go ahead.
Get your screenshots in.
I think we just stumbled across the hot dogs.
Uh-oh.
Hot dogs!
We're tourists.
Oh!
Yeah.
Where are you guys from?
Texas.
Oh.
Yeah.
Just a hot dog or...?
Oh, two Dodger dogs.
Then, uh...
Compliments on your rights.
Alright!
Yeah!
That gentleman has no idea that he just made our day.
I bought a baseball for my souvenir collection, and we made our way to our seats.
Here's our spot!
Baseball!
I just can't get over this.
This is absolutely beautiful.
People are piling into their seats.
This really does feel like an American bucket list item.
Yes.
This is one of the oldest baseball fields in America.
You ready to have your first Dodger Dog?
I've been waiting all day.
Haley and I are some catch-up fiends.
My dad used to tell me, "Son, there's a point in every baseball game where you finally let go."
I had that moment during the national anthem.
It doesn't get much more American than this, does it?
Before long, the game Had begun, and we found ourselves cheering for anything that resembled action on the baseball field.
Double play!
Yes!
We got to watch Shohei Ohtani, one of the best baseball players, get a base hit.
Gosh, he's so cool.
We also got to watch him score a run, which is a pretty cool experience in Dodger Stadium.
I'm about to surprise Haley with a treat.
Thank you.
It's ice cream in a baseball helmet.
Haley!
Me and Haley are souvenir maxing right now.
Look at all this stuff we have from the baseball game so far.
I'm going to be launching these bucket list boxes in a few episodes, so I just want to make sure I'm not missing anything.
Let me ask Sidekick to do an audit of my store to see if there's any tasks that I still need to complete.
Looks like there's still a few things for me to do, but let's start by fixing the inventory.
Luckily, Shopify makes it very easy to accurately update my products from zero to one.
And after completing Sidekick's checklist, our website is just about ready to go.
Start your business alongside me and Sidekick by signing up for your trial at shopify.com slash Ryan.
Thank you, Shopify.
Ricky, what did you just say?
So if you go to the guest services counter at Dodgers Stadium, tell them it's your first game, they give you a pin that says first Dodgers game.
Come on, thank you for that information.
Is there a place to pick up a pin as a first time Dodgers guest?
Yeah, go down to the first services.
Another souvenir unlocked.
Ricky, we got him!
At one point, the entire stadium started doing The Wave, which is way cooler in person than on TV.
Haley and I got a photo for our scrapbook.
Ricky took this.
Shout out, Ricky.
Photo creds to her.
And before we knew it, our night at Dodger Stadium ended with a Dodger win.
They won the game.
Back from the baseball game, we are in our hotel.
We have a late night tonight and a very early morning tomorrow.
Like, super early.
Our earliest morning yet.
And we've had some early mornings.
I think tomorrow's tourist attraction is our longest travel day as well.
So we'll be traveling for like five and a half hours before we even get the chance to travel another two hours to get there.
A road trip?
And a flight.
It's multiple.
It's quite a remote tourist attraction.
But that's besides the point.
We need to focus on Los Angeles and update our bucket list book.
This is our top 10 tourist attraction ranking list so far.
And now we are going to add Los Angeles to the mix.
New York City is currently in first place, Las Vegas currently in last.
It's okay.
Haley did a great job decorating the scrapbook page today.
Honestly, some of my favorite photos we've gotten from the whole trip today.
As you know, we're not just ranking these tourist attractions willy-nilly.
No, we have criteria.
Experience, scenery, and magic.
Similar to New York City, Los Angeles is beyond a tourist attraction.
You can't capture it in one day.
It's a huge city with tons of things to do.
You want to start with experience?
Yes.
One, two, three, seven.
I almost did seven.
Now that we've done so many, I'm starting to think about the others and what we rated those because we ranked New York City eight.
And I think Los Angeles experience wise might just be about one point lower, mostly because we spent two and a half hours of our day in traffic.
That's true.
It's just true.
Are you good with seven?
Yeah, I would say seven.
All right, boom.
Next, scenery rating.
What are the visuals?
What does it look like?
You take it all in and what do you feel?
One, two, three, eight.
Nice.
Eight is a really good score, especially for an entire city.
Laying in that grass earlier today was the most free I felt in maybe years.
I could tell you reacted similarly to how our Chihuahua does to a large patch of grass.
Scenery rating, eight.
Last but not least, magic rating on three.
One, two, three, seven.
Dang, okay.
Out of everything, I think the Dodgers game was the most magical.
The atmosphere was so good.
The food was fun.
I love a baseball.
Game.
I haven't been to a baseball game in so long.
The visuals are just so satisfying.
They do a really good job making the game entertaining in real life.
Because I feel like when you watch it on TV, with the commercials and everything, it feels very slow.
But it feels so fast-paced in real life.
Also, the Dodgers are one of the best teams in baseball, so getting to watch them live, that's a treat.
Also, we ate treats out of helmets.
Magic rating, 7.
That means Los Angeles has the same score as Washington, D.C., and we have decided to put it just below at rank number 6.
Haley, we have quite the list here, only two more.
That's so crazy.
I know.
It's wild seeing New York City in first place.
I had no idea how these were going to stack up.
I cannot believe we have been able to do all these in the past eight days, both logistically and just in general.
What a blessing.
We are having so much fun.
We are so grateful to be doing this series.
You guys are incredible.
Good night.
We will see you soon.
Only two more tourist attractions to go.
My goodness, where has the time gone?
Will New York City be number one, or will it be dethroned?
Keep watching to find out.
Click the video on screen.
I'll see you there.